<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Privacy policy and terms of use on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</title>
    <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Privacy policy and terms of use on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © AgroFIMS 2020 [Terms of Use and Privacy Policy](https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/)</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/privacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/privacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Effective date: January 01, 2020
 WHAT TYPE OF PERSONAL DATA DO WE COLLECT FROM USERS AND HOW DO WE MANAGE IT?  When signing up to AgroFIMS, we ask you for information such as your name, last name, email, name of organization you work with, and the country you live in. Providing this information is mandatory to create an account and use AgroFIMS. We respect user privacy; accordingly, any personally identifiable information you provide is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged with AgroFIMS and will only be used for internal purposes in accordance with site-specific policies, or in ways to which you have explicitly consented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use of AgroFIMS</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/use/</guid>
      <description>Effective date: January 01, 2020
 YOUR PRIVACY  We respect user privacy and manage any personally identifiable information collected by us from you through AgroFIMS in accordance with our PRIVACY POLICY.
COPYRIGHT  Copyright © 2019 International Potato Center – CIP
AgroFIMS is an online interface conceived to standardizes agronomic data collection. CIP holds the title to the online AgroFIMS and to the materials and content generated by AgroFIMS unless otherwise specified.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>