<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KDSmart on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</title>
    <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KDSmart on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © AgroFIMS 2020 [Terms of Use and Privacy Policy](https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/)</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Set in production mode</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/productionmode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/productionmode/</guid>
      <description>The application downloaded is in Demo DB mode. To enable all the functionalities the mode Production has to be enabled.
 In the home screen, click on the menu icon on the top left, and select Settings.    2.	In the Settings menu, click on Active Database.  Select Production.   To go back to the home screen, click on the arrow at the top left.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export AgroFIMS fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/exportkdsmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/exportkdsmart/</guid>
      <description>To upload an AgroFIMS fieldbook in KDSmart, you have to first export the AgroFIMS fieldbook as a .kdx file.
  Select Experiments in the Menu and select the experiment of our choice.   Go to the Fieldbooks tab and open the fieldbook of your choice by clicking on open icon.   Click on the cloud icon at the top right of the window.   Click on Build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Send KDSmart file to mobile device</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/sendtokdsmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/sendtokdsmart/</guid>
      <description>Once you have downloaded a .kdx file, you have to send it to the device where KDSmart is installed. For this you have three options:
  Via email: send an email to yourself or the data collector, with the .kdx file attached. Open this email on the mobile device where KDSmart is installed and download the .kdx file in the folder ‘’Download’’ of the mobile device.
  Via a cloud storage service: On your laptop save the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open fieldbook in KDSmart</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/openinkdsmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/openinkdsmart/</guid>
      <description>Once the .kdx file is stored in your mobile device, you can open it in KDSmart following this tutorial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identify the plots</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/identifyplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/identifyplot/</guid>
      <description>In KDSmart the plots can be named either by their number or by the number of their column, row and block.
  Download a trial (cf. KDSmart tutorial ).
  Click on the three dots at the top left (1).
  Select Trials (2).   Select your trial in the list to open Trial Details.
  Click on the edit icon next to Plot identification.   Select Plot if you want to identify the plots by their number, select Block/Field Column/Field Row if you prefer to identify the plots with their Block/Column and Row numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to find the information filled in AgroFIMS</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/findinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/findinfo/</guid>
      <description>Metadata and measurements filled in AgroFIMS are lited in the Trail details part of KDSMart. To find it:
  Click on the three dots at the top left of KDSmart screen (1).
  Select Trials (2).   Select your trial in the list to open the Trial Details page of your experiment.
  Experiment objective is noted as “Note“ (3)
  Measurements (Crop, Phenology, Soil, Management practices to be collected in the field) are listed as “Traits”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scoring panel</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/scoringpanel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/scoringpanel/</guid>
      <description>In the Scoring Panel of a trait you can find more details about it.
  Start scoring a trial (cf. KDSmart tutorial ).
  Click on a Trait to open the Scoring Panel and get trait information.
  (1) TraitAlias : short name of the trait.
(2) Measurement timing : when to measure the trait.
(3) Type of data
(4) Trait validation rule : maximum and minimum possible value of the trait.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>