<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AgroFIMS Help Page on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</title>
    <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AgroFIMS Help Page on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © AgroFIMS 2020 [Terms of Use and Privacy Policy](https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/about/</guid>
      <description>The Agronomy Field Information Management System (AgroFIMS) allows users to create fieldbooks to collect agronomic data that is already tied to a metadata standard (the CG Core Metadata Schema, aligned with the standard Dublin Core), and semantic standards like the Agronomy Ontology (AgrO), generating data that is Findable, Accessible, Interoperable, and Reusable (FAIR) at collection. AgroFIMS therefore standardizes data collection and description for easy aggregation and inter-linking across disparate datasets. By December 2020 you will be able to export the fieldbooks you create to the Android-based KDSmart or Field Book applications for data collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding a crop or a variety to the experiment</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop/adding_a_crop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop/adding_a_crop/</guid>
      <description>1.	Select the type of cropping system of your experiment. Currently the choices are: Monocrop, Intercrop or Relay crop.2.	Select the crop’s common name. If the crop is not listed, select ‘’Other’’ and specify the crop common name. If “Intercrop” or “Relay crop” are selected, AgroFIMS will require you to add at least 2 crops. To add more, click on “add crop”.3.	Enter the variety name. You can enter as many varieties as needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding personnel</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/addpersonnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/addpersonnel/</guid>
      <description>Click on the button Add Personnel to add a new person to the experiment. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a new experiment</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experiments/</guid>
      <description> In the menu select Experiments Click on the button New Experiment Enter an experiment name Click on the button Create to validate  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/site/</guid>
      <description>Before creating your fielbook, you may want to create the site of your experiment.
 Select Sites in the Menu. Click on the button New site. Fill the information about the site type, site name, country name and administrative divisions using text boxes and picklists as appropriate. You can zoom in the map to help you find the name of your location, but you cannot use the map to directly pinpoint the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/privacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/privacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Effective date: January 01, 2020
 WHAT TYPE OF PERSONAL DATA DO WE COLLECT FROM USERS AND HOW DO WE MANAGE IT?  When signing up to AgroFIMS, we ask you for information such as your name, last name, email, name of organization you work with, and the country you live in. Providing this information is mandatory to create an account and use AgroFIMS. We respect user privacy; accordingly, any personally identifiable information you provide is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged with AgroFIMS and will only be used for internal purposes in accordance with site-specific policies, or in ways to which you have explicitly consented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signing Up</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/signup/</guid>
      <description> Go to AgroFIMS. Enter your email, password, name, last name, organization and country. Click Create. Your account has been created. You can Log in and start using AgroFIMS.  An email will be sent to your mailbox to confirm your account. Don’t forget to check your spam folder if you don’t see the email in your inbox!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AgroFIMS License</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/license/</guid>
      <description>License text without any modification
 License All the source of AGROFIMS is under GPL-3 license. For further details about this licence, please click on link.
GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007
Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. http://fsf.org/ Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
 Preamble The GNU General Public License is a free, copyleft license for software and other kinds of works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiment ID</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experimentid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experimentid/</guid>
      <description>The Experiment ID is a code generated by AgroFIMS to uniquely name experiments. It is made up of the 2 first letters of Experiment name + the 2 first letters of Experiment project name + unique number</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home screen</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/homescreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/homescreen/</guid>
      <description> Button to open and close the Menu Menu  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loading my info</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/myinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/myinfo/</guid>
      <description>You can start by adding your profile information using the button ‘’ Load my info’’ . This will auto-fill the boxes with information registered in your profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging in</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/log/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/log/</guid>
      <description> At the upper right corner of the Home page, click on and select Log In Enter your email and your password. Click Log In  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/open/</guid>
      <description>Open tools for open science
In the AgroFIMS project, we are strong advocates of enriching the community with open tools for agronomists and researchers in general. AgroFIMS is composed by:
  a web application based on Angular, HTML and Javascript;
  R-packages to facilitate the design and analysis of agronomic data;
  Pythons and Java rutines to facilitate the conversion of AgroFIMS files to mobile applications such as KDSmart and Field Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use of AgroFIMS</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/use/</guid>
      <description>Effective date: January 01, 2020
 YOUR PRIVACY  We respect user privacy and manage any personally identifiable information collected by us from you through AgroFIMS in accordance with our PRIVACY POLICY.
COPYRIGHT  Copyright © 2019 International Potato Center – CIP
AgroFIMS is an online interface conceived to standardizes agronomic data collection. CIP holds the title to the online AgroFIMS and to the materials and content generated by AgroFIMS unless otherwise specified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viewing site information</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/viewsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/viewsite/</guid>
      <description> Go to Sites in the Menu. Click on the eye icon next to the site you want to get information about.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Fieldbook ID?</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop/fieldbook_id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop/fieldbook_id/</guid>
      <description>Fieldbook ID is a unique identifier created by AgroFIMS to identify your experiment. It is made of the concatenation of the following information: F_Cropping type_Crop name_Experiment start date_Country. “F” stands for Fieldbook in this case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding a Funding agency – Project management entity – Experiment lead</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/agency/</guid>
      <description>Click on the + button to add a new line. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AgroFIMS workflow</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/workflow/</guid>
      <description>AgroFIMS works in collaboration with the Android applications like KDSmart, ODK Collect and Field Book apps to provide a complete workflow to manage data for the creation of a fieldbook to the data analysis. Below are the different steps to follow to create, collect, analyze and save data using AgroFIMS: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to create a fieldbook in AgroFIMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May I import a list of varieties or genotypes?</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop/import_variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop/import_variety/</guid>
      <description>It is not currently possible to import a list of varieties or genotypes. You have to manually enter your list in the text box: Variety name(s)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing personnel</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/removepersonnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/removepersonnel/</guid>
      <description>Click on the red cross at the top right of the personnel box to remove it. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating a site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/updatesite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/updatesite/</guid>
      <description>A site cannot be updated. You must create a new site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating your password</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/updatepassword/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/updatepassword/</guid>
      <description> Log in. Click on at the top right corner of the Home page. Select Autentication Enter your current password and a new password. Click ‘’Update password’’. Your password has been updated and you can now log in with your new password.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modifying your profile</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/modifyprofile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/modifyprofile/</guid>
      <description>You can view your profile information by selecting Account &amp;gt; Profile in the Menu. If you wish to update your profile information, please send an email to agrofims@cgiar.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing a Funding agency – Project management entity – Experiment lead</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/removeagency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/removeagency/</guid>
      <description>Click on the cross at the upper right side of the line to remove it. There is a minimum of one line per category. If you want to remove the information in this line, you can erase the name typed. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Requesting a new password</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/newpassword/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/newpassword/</guid>
      <description> At the upper right corner of the Home page, click on  Select Forgot your password? Enter your email and click on Reset my password A new password will be sent to your email address.  Don’t forget to check your spam folder
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/site/</guid>
      <description>In this section you can describe the experimental site and its surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a site ID?</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/siteid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/siteid/</guid>
      <description>The site ID is a unique identifier automatically generated by AgroFIMS to distinguish the sites in your sites list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deleting a Site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/deletesite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/deletesite/</guid>
      <description> Go to Sites in the Menu. Click on bin icon next to the site you want to delete.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May I leave a case blank?</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/blankcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/blankcase/</guid>
      <description>The mandatory fields are marked with a red asterisk. All other fields may be left blank. However, we recommend that you provide as much information about your experiment as possible. Robust metadata will allow better understanding and interpretation of your data set, and greatly augment its discovery and re-use in the immediate and distant future, assuring that your data continues to provide value well after collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to create a fieldbook in AgroFIMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>old page</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/manageaccount/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/features/managingyouraccount/manageaccount/</guid>
      <description>Signing Up  Go to AgroFIMS. Enter your email, password, name, last name, organization and country. Click Create. Your account has been created. You can Log in and start using AgroFIMS. An email will be sent to your mailbox to confirm your account. Don’t forget to check your spam folder if you don’t see the email in your inbox!  Logging in  At the upper right corner of the Home page, click on and select Log In Enter your email and your password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fertilizer</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fertilizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fertilizer/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to add fertilizer applications in your protocol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management practices</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/management-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/management-practices/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to add management practices in your protocol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crop measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop-measurement/</guid>
      <description>In this section you can select and describe the measurements to be made on the crops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phenology measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/phenology-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/phenology-measurements/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to create a fieldbook in AgroFIMS.
Phenology measurements 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soil measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/soil-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/soil-measurements/</guid>
      <description>This section is dedicated to the selection of soil measurements to make during the experiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/weather-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/weather-measurements/</guid>
      <description>This section is dedicated to the selection of weather measurements to make during the experiment.
Selecting a weather measurement  Select a measurement in the drop-down list. You can either scroll through the list or delete the default and type the name of your measurement – the auto-complete feature will select the term if the measurement is in the list. Once you have found your measurement, select it and click on .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>