<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AgroFIMS Help Page on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</title>
    <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AgroFIMS Help Page on AgroFIMS Help Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © AgroFIMS 2020 [Terms of Use and Privacy Policy](https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 11:02:05 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/about/</guid>
      <description>The Agronomy Field Information Management System (AgroFIMS) allows users to create fieldbooks to collect agronomic data. The fieldbook is already tied to a metadata standard (the CG Core Metadata Schema, aligned with the industry standard Dublin Core Metadata Schema and required by CGIAR and many other repositories). The data variables and protocol parameters in AgroFIMS fieldbooks align with semantic standards like the and semantic standards like the Agronomy Ontology (AgrO). This a priori compliance with data standards facilitates data to be Findable, Accessible, Interoperable, and Reusable (FAIR) at collection, making it easier to interpret and aggregate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding personnel</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/addpersonnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/addpersonnel/</guid>
      <description>Click on the button Add Personnel to add a new person to the experiment, and then add information about him/her. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a new experiment</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experiments/</guid>
      <description> In the menu select Experiments. Click on the button New Experiment.  Enter an experiment name. Click on the button Create to validate your new entry.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/createfieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/createfieldbook/</guid>
      <description>Click on the button Add Fieldbook. Choose a country in the drop-down list. Choose a site in the drop-down list.    To be able to create a new fieldbook, you must have created your site first. To create your site, click on Create new site.
If your site doesn&amp;rsquo;t appear in the site list, check the list by clicking on Sites in the navigation menu. If the site is not listed, it may not have been saved during its creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/site/</guid>
      <description>Before creating your fielbook, you may want to create the site where your experiment is to occur.
 Select Sites in the navigation menu at left on the home page. Click on the button New site. Add information about the site type, site name, country name and administrative divisions using text boxes and picklists as appropriate. You can zoom into the map to find the name of your location, but you cannot use the map to directly pinpoint the site and have all the administrative information automatically filled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export AgroFIMS fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/exportfieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/exportfieldbook/</guid>
      <description>To upload an AgroFIMS fieldbook to Field Book, you have to first export the AgroFIMS fieldbook as a .zip file and then unzip it.
  Go to Experiments in the left-hand panel menu and select the experiment of your choice by clicking on the “open” icon (square with an arrow through it).   Go to the Fieldbooks tab at the top.
  Open the fieldbook of your choice by clicking on the “open” icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/privacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/privacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Effective date: January 01, 2020
 WHAT TYPE OF PERSONAL DATA DO WE COLLECT FROM USERS AND HOW DO WE MANAGE IT?  When signing up to AgroFIMS, we ask you for information such as your name, last name, email, name of organization you work with, and the country you live in. Providing this information is mandatory to create an account and use AgroFIMS. We respect user privacy; accordingly, any personally identifiable information you provide is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged with AgroFIMS and will only be used for internal purposes in accordance with site-specific policies, or in ways to which you have explicitly consented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set in production mode</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/productionmode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/productionmode/</guid>
      <description>The application downloaded is in Demo DB mode. To enable all the functionalities the mode Production has to be enabled.
 In the home screen, click on the menu icon on the top left, and select Settings.    2.	In the Settings menu, click on Active Database  Select Production   To go back to the home screen, click on the arrow at the top left.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signing Up</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/signup/</guid>
      <description>Go to AgroFIMS.
  Click on Register.   Enter your email, first name, last name, email, affiliation, and country.
  Click Register.
  An email will be sent to your mailbox with a link to activate your account and a password.
  Click on the link to activate your password.
  Go to AgroFIMS to log in. We recommend that you modify the password sent and change it frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specifying the design</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/specifydesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/specifydesign/</guid>
      <description>To specify the design of the experiment:
 Select the experimental design of your experiment using the drop-down list. Select the experimental unit (plot, field, pot). Enter the dimensions of the experimental unit selected and select a unit to express the size of the experimental unit using the dropdown list.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Send the files to mobile device</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/sendtofieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/sendtofieldbook/</guid>
      <description>Once you have created a .zip file, you have to send it to the device where Field Book is installed. For this you have three options:
•	Via email: send an email to yourself or the data collector, with the .csv and .trt files attached. Open this email on the mobile device where Field Book is installed and download the files.
•	Via the cloud: On your laptop save the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AgroFIMS License</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/license/</guid>
      <description>License text without any modification
 License All the source of AGROFIMS is under GPL-3 license. For further details about this licence, please click on link.
GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007
Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. http://fsf.org/ Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
 Preamble The GNU General Public License is a free, copyleft license for software and other kinds of works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AgroFIMS workflow</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/workflow/</guid>
      <description>AgroFIMS works in collaboration with Android applications like KDSmart, Field Book and ODK Collect to provide a complete standards-compliant workflow, from picking data variables and experimental protocol parameters to create an Excel fieldbook, through data analysis and upload to data repositories. Below are the different steps to follow to create, collect, analyze and save data using AgroFIMS. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining the treatment</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/definingdesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/definingdesign/</guid>
      <description>A treatment is a combination of factor levels. A factor is a controlled independent variable whose levels are set by the experimenter. Each factor has two or more levels (i.e. two or more different values).
To define the treatment of the experiment:
 Specify the number of treatments and repetitions (or blocks). Select a factor in the list. If the factor is not listed, select ‘’Other’’ and specify the name of the factor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing a fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/editfieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/editfieldbook/</guid>
      <description>Click on Experiments on the navigation menu.
  Open the experiment of your choice by clicking on the Open icon on the right side of the experiment line.   Go to the Fieldbooks tab.
  Click on the Open icon on the right side of the Fieldbook line to open it.
  When you edit a fieldbook, only the edited version is saved. You won’t be able to retrieve the original version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiment ID</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experimentid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/experimentid/</guid>
      <description>The Experiment ID is a code generated by AgroFIMS to uniquely name experiments. It is made up of the first two letters of experiment name + the first two letters of experiment project name + a unique number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export AgroFIMS fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/exportkdsmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/exportkdsmart/</guid>
      <description>To upload an AgroFIMS fieldbook in KDSmart, you have to first export the AgroFIMS fieldbook as a .kdx file.
  Select Experiments in the Menu and select the experiment of our choice.   Go to the Fieldbooks tab and open the fieldbook of your choice by clicking on “open” icon (square with an arrow through it).   Click on the cloud icon at the top right of the window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing a fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/importfieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/importfieldbook/</guid>
      <description>It is currently not possible to import an existing fieldbook into AgroFIMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loading my info</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/myinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/myinfo/</guid>
      <description>You can start by adding your profile information using the button Load my info. This will auto-fill the boxes with information registered in your profile.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging in</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/log/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/log/</guid>
      <description> Go to AgroFIMS. Enter your email and your password. Click Login.   If the login screen is not open when you reach AgroFIMS, click on LOGIN at the top right corner of the Home page.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/sourcecode/open/</guid>
      <description>Open tools for open science
In the AgroFIMS project, we are strong advocates of enriching the community with open tools for agronomists and researchers in general. AgroFIMS is composed by:
  a web application based on Angular, HTML and Javascript;
  R-packages to facilitate the design and analysis of agronomic data;
  Pythons and Java rutines to facilitate the conversion of AgroFIMS files to mobile applications such as KDSmart and Field Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use of AgroFIMS</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/policyterms/use/</guid>
      <description>Effective date: January 01, 2020
 YOUR PRIVACY  We respect user privacy and manage any personally identifiable information collected by us from you through AgroFIMS in accordance with our PRIVACY POLICY.
COPYRIGHT  Copyright © 2019 International Potato Center – CIP
AgroFIMS is an online interface conceived to standardizes agronomic data collection. CIP holds the title to the online AgroFIMS and to the materials and content generated by AgroFIMS unless otherwise specified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viewing site information</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/viewsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/viewsite/</guid>
      <description> Go to Sites in the navigation menu at left of the home page. Click on the blue eye icon next to the site about which you want information.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Send KDSmart file to mobile device</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/sendtokdsmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/sendtokdsmart/</guid>
      <description>Once you have downloaded a .kdx file, you have to send it to the device where KDSmart is installed. For this you have three options:
  Via email: send an email to yourself or the data collector, with the .kdx file attached. Open this email on the mobile device where KDSmart is installed and download the .kdx file in the folder ‘’Download’’ of the mobile device.
  Via a cloud: On your laptop save the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding a Funding agency</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/agency/</guid>
      <description>To add a funding agency, a project management entity or an experiment lead, click on the +Add button to add a new line. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having only 1 replication</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/replication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/replication/</guid>
      <description>It is not possible to design an experiment with only one replication, thus, AgroFIMS requires that you add at least two replications. Currently AgroFIMS does not allow data collection from demonstration experiments and farmer surveys, which may not be replicated. This capability will be developed in the next version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home screen</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/homescreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/homescreen/</guid>
      <description> Button to open and close the Menu Profile settings, log in and to log out Navigation menu  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing a fieldbook</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/deletefieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fieldbook/deletefieldbook/</guid>
      <description>  Click on Experiments on the navigation menu.
  Open the experiment of your choice by clicking on the Open icon on the right side of the experiment line.   Go to the Fieldbooks tab.
  Click on the red bin icon on the right side of the fieldbook line to remove it.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing personnel</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/removepersonnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/personnel/removepersonnel/</guid>
      <description>Click on the red x at the top right of the personnel box to remove a person’s information. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the files in your mobile memory</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/editfieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/editfieldbook/</guid>
      <description>  Save the .csv file in the folder field_import of the main folder fieldBook created by the app on the mobile device.
  Save the .trt file in the trait folder of the folder fieldBook created by the app on the mobile device
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating your password</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/updatepassword/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/updatepassword/</guid>
      <description> Log in to AgroFIMS. Click on Profile settings at the top right corner of the Home page. Select Authentication.  Enter your current password and a new one. Click Update password.  Your password has been updated and you can now log in with your new password.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a site ID?</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/siteid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/siteid/</guid>
      <description>The site ID is a unique identifier automatically generated by AgroFIMS to distinguish the sites in your list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding your factor</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/findingfactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/findingfactor/</guid>
      <description>Scroll through the dropdown menu or start typing the name of the factor; AgroFIMS will narrow down the possibilities for you. The factors are listed using broader categories. This means that if you want to test different amounts of urea, the factor you should select is Fertilizer amount. If you want to test different potato varieties, the factor will be Crop variety.
  If the factor is not in the list, select Other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open fieldbook in KDSmart</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/openinkdsmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/openinkdsmart/</guid>
      <description>Once the .kdx file is stored in your mobile device, you can open it in KDSmart following this tutorial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open the files in Field Book</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/openfieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/fieldbookapp/openfieldbook/</guid>
      <description>Open Field Book.
  Go Fields.   Click on the + at the top right and select Local storage.   Select the .csv file exported from AgroFIMS, and then validate the radio button next to it.   Go back to the main menu and select Traits.   Click on the three dots at the top right and select ‘’Import/Export’’.   Select ‘’Import’’ and then ‘’Local storage’’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing a Funding agency</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/removeagency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/removeagency/</guid>
      <description>To remove a funding agency, a project management entity or an experiment lead, click on the red x at the upper right of the information field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Requesting a new password</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/newpassword/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/newpassword/</guid>
      <description>  Go to AgroFIMS.
  On the login screen select Forgot your pwd?.   Enter your email and click on Reset my password.
  A new password will be sent to your email address. Don’t forget to check your spam folder.
  If the login screen is not open when you reach AgroFIMS, click on LOGIN at the top right corner of the Home page.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/site/</guid>
      <description>Once you have created a fieldbook, you can describe your the experimental site and its surroundings.
•	Site information - specifies the country and name of your experiment site.
•	Site description - provides details on the surroundings of your experiment site.
•	Soil classification might be known before the experiment starts and detailed in this section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating a site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/updatesite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/updatesite/</guid>
      <description>A site cannot be updated. You must create a new site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deleting a Site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/deletesite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/deletesite/</guid>
      <description> Go to Sites in the navigation menu at left of the home page. Click on bin icon next to the site you want to delete.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identify the plots</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/identifyplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/identifyplot/</guid>
      <description>In KDSmart the plots can be named either by their number or by the number of their column, row and block.
  Download a trial (cf. KDSmart tutorial  )
  Click on the three dots at the top left (1)
  Select “Trials” (2)   Select your trial in the list to open “Trial Details”
  Click on the edit icon next to “Plot identification”   Select “Plot” if you want to identify the plots by their number, select &amp;ldquo;Block/Field Column/Field Row” if you prefer to identify the plots with their Block/Column and Row numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving a field blank?</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/blankcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/experiments/blankcase/</guid>
      <description>Mandatory fields are marked with an asterisk. All other fields may be left blank. However, we recommend that you provide as much information about your experiment as possible.
Robust metadata will allow better understanding and interpretation of your data set, and greatly augment its discovery and re-use in the immediate and distant future, assuring that your data continues to provide value well after collection.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modifying your profile information</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/modifyprofile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/about/managingyouraccount/modifyprofile/</guid>
      <description>You can only view your profile information by selecting Profile settings at the top right corner of the Home page and then Profile. If you wish to update your profile information, please send an email to agrofims@cgiar.org .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Type and amount factor</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/typeandamountfactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/typeandamountfactor/</guid>
      <description>To allow a wide range of treatments, some factors have been grouped together. For example, the irrigation amount factor has been grouped with the irrigation type factor. This way it is possible to compare different types of irrigation with different amounts (Sprinkler irrigation 200ml versus Drip irrigation 300ml ).
For these factors:
 Select the factor in the list. Specify the type of factor. Enter the level and their units. Click +, if you need to add another type of the same factor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fertilizer factor</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/fertilizerfactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/fertilizerfactor/</guid>
      <description>For the Fertilizer type and amount factor you have the possibility to calculate the nutrient amount that will be applied to the field and to specify the management practices.
  Select Fertilizer type and amount in the factor list.
  Once you have specified the fertilizer type, levels and number of application splits, click on Application details.   A pop-up window will appear.
  The nutrient content in the product is added by default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&#39;t find my site</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/findsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingasite/findsite/</guid>
      <description> If your site doesn&amp;rsquo;t appear in the site list, check the list by clicking on Sites in the navigation menu. If the site is not listed, it may not have been saved during its creation. You may create the site again by clicking on the blue button + New site.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to find the information filled in AgroFIMS</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/findinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/collect/kdsmart/findinfo/</guid>
      <description>In Trial Details   Click on the three dots at the top left of KDSmart screen (1).
  Select “Trials” (2).   Select your trial in the list to open the Trial Details page of your experiment.
  Experiment objective is noted as Note (3)
  Measurements (Crop, Phenology, Soil, Management practices to be collected in the field) are listed as “Traits”. (4)
  Experiment, personnel, site, crop and design information are listed under “Trial attributes”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fertilizer</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fertilizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/fertilizer/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to add fertilizer applications in your protocol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrient factor</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/nutrientfactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/design/nutrientfactor/</guid>
      <description>For the Nutrient type and amount factor you have the possibility to calculate the amount of product to be applied in the field and to specify the management practices.
  Select Nutrient type and amount in the factor list.
  Select the crop to which you will apply the nutrient, in intercrop and relay crop experiments.
  Once you have specified the type, levels and number of application splits, click on Application details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management practices</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/management-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/management-practices/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to add management practices in your protocol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crop measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/crop-measurement/</guid>
      <description>In this section you can select and describe the measurements to be made on the crops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phenology measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/phenology-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/phenology-measurements/</guid>
      <description>Find below the steps to create a fieldbook in AgroFIMS.
Phenology measurements 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soil measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/soil-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/soil-measurements/</guid>
      <description>This section is dedicated to the selection of soil measurements to make during the experiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather measurements</title>
      <link>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/weather-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agrofims.github.io/helpdocs/creatingafieldbook/weather-measurements/</guid>
      <description>This section is dedicated to the selection of weather measurements to make during the experiment.
Selecting a weather measurement  Select a measurement in the drop-down list. You can either scroll through the list or delete the default and type the name of your measurement – the auto-complete feature will select the term if the measurement is in the list. Once you have found your measurement, select it and click on .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>